(Amy:)-Included?
-Yes!
(Sheldon:)Not sold separately.
(Sheldon:)Although, the PS4
uses cool new GDDR5 RAM,
(Sheldon:)while the Xbox One is still using
the conventional DDR3 memory.
(Amy:)Why would they still
be using DDR3?
(Amy:)Are they nuts?
(Sheldon:)See? That's what I thought.
(Sheldon:)But then they go and throw in
an ESRAM buffer.
-Whoa. Wait a second. Who's "they"?
-Xbox.
-You're kidding!
-No, I am not!
(Sheldon:)And this ESRAM buffer
should totally bridge
(Sheldon:)the 100-gigabit-per-second
bandwidth gap
(Sheldon:)between the two RAM types.
(Amy:)This is a nightmare.
How will you ever make a decision?
I don't know!
What should I do?
(Amy:)Please pass the butter!
(Penny:)Okay, it's not me, right?
This script is terrible.
(Penny:)Yeah.
I had higher hopes for a movie called